When I saw her pretending to play dumb
I knew that was my chance.
At that point, I kinda figured…
"Amamiya probably likes her."
And I'm sure it's mutual.
I could tell.
But I could also tell she was never
gonna make the first move.
She'll make all sorts of excuses,
keep pretending not to notice
And pathetically do whatever it takes
to protect herself from getting hurt.
She's a weakling who gets her
validation and happiness from
others instead of herself.
A passive girl who just sits and waits.
Ugh.
I really hate her.
EPISODE 15
CLOUDS AND RAIN
The Meiten band's gonna be
putting on a concert soon.
Did you hear Akahoshi talking about it?
Oh…
You know what, I think the
guys did say something.
You maybe wanna go together?
My friend's performing in it,
so I wanna go support.
But I'm too chicken to go by myself.
Sure. Let's do it.
I'll ask around,
see if anyone else wants to come too.
Hm…
The bigger audience the better, right?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Ah. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to bother you.
I just figured it was easier and faster
to call than type it all out in a text,
y'know?
Easier and faster, huh?
Well,
I'll reach out
again closer to the concert.
Cool. Sounds good.
Hm.
LIFT
SIDE PLANK
The rain… It just won't stop.
MEITEN HIGH SCHOOL
I like you.
Today, when I run into Yota in class
how should I approach him?
Would it hurt him
to act like nothing happened?
Avoiding him would hurt more,
wouldn't it?
Wait.
Aren't I hurting him more by not
being able to return his feelings
in the first place?
What should I do?
Miki.
Morning.
You ready for the quiz?
The one for Japanese class?
Huh?! That was today?!
Crap!
There's still time. Don't worry.
You just need to memorize the handout.
Oh, there you go again!
"You just have to memorize it!"
Like it's the easiest thing in the world.
Seriously…
Hey, don't stress.
You've got this.
Hey, Yota! We're goin' on ahead.
Oh, wait up.
Well, See you later.
Why's he gotta be so nice?
BANANA DRINK
GENTLE SWEETNESS OF RIPE BANANA
So, Miki. Something happened, right?
No, nothing happened.
Here, try this.
SIP
Tell me, Minato.
Hm?
You casually date chicks you're not
into all the time, right?
Woah. Random.
And kinda rude.
Ever turn someone down
after they confessed their feelings?
Uh…
- I guess not.
- Why not?
It's not that I had
a reason to date them.
But I guess I also didn't have a reason…
Not to date them.
Okay, but afterward
do you ever regret deciding to date them?
Since I'm usually the dumpee
they clearly regret dating me.
Hence, the dumping.
If they said they didn't want to be
with me, then that was that.
There was no point
in fighting it or begging.
I wonder…
if it was painful for them knowing
you had different feelings than they do.
UH, WHAT?
AM I BEING ATTACKED?
GUILT
Someday, when you finally
fall in love with someone
and they don't care about you at all,
I hope it really pushes you
over the deep end, man.
Yeah. Possibly.
The pain of unrequited feelings…
I get it now.
I never thought of it that way.
I feel like I've been a jerk
to all the girls I've dated.
So then that's how it goes,
it never works out.
Yeah- Wait, hold up.
Wait. Uh-
Are you trying to tell me somone
confessed their feelings to you
and you're debating whether
you should turn them down?
Oh crap.
I just said the wrong thing, didn't I?
No, I…
Already did.
Huh?
That's what happened. Guess it's over.
Well hey,
since I knew nothing
would come of it anyway…
I'm glad I got it out
and don't have to keep it bottled up.
You are? Really?
Yep.
But,
I'm also bummed thinking
like "Aw, it's over."
Now it feels like there's
this giant empty space inside me,
that that feeling used to fill.
How should I put it?
Now I just want… to fill that void.
Yota
Is he crying…? You can cry.
- Huh?
- Uh…
He's not crying…
Oh, um…
I-I thought you might need
something to cry into.
Thanks, but I'm okay.
Is this something people
usually cry over?
I wouldn't know, I can't cry.
Don't get me wrong, I feel sad at times.
Graduation ceremonies…
or after losing a big game, but…
at some point
I gave up on getting worked up over
things because that's just how life is.
When my emotions get too big
I let them escape through tears.
But,
Yota keeps them all bottled up inside.
I mean, I like this guy,
but if I'm honest,
I've only ever liked him as a friend.
And not as a boyfriend or anything.
Back in junior high
I guess I dated a few guys
here and there but,
Whenever they would give me their number,
I would feel this… I don't know…
a feeling I could never quite place.
They'd give off vibes of
"someone I could end up dating."
I FEEL LIKE HE MIGHT BE A GOOD GUY
I felt butterflies in my stomach
and dated them thinking I
might like them back, but…
I GOT DUMPED AGAIN!
It never worked out in the end,
and every time…
I felt like I was being rejected.
FINE, WHATEVER I'LL FORGET ABOUT IT…
I wasn't really seeing
them for who they were either.
- So…
- Hmph…
I've never- Never had a real relationship.
I was just happy that
someone liked me, y'know?
So if I date this guy despite not
feeling the same way yet… that's like…
I'd be leading him on
just to not hurt his feelings.
And I- I just know
I'll end up hating myself in the end.
So
I don't think I'm in the wrong here.
But I feel…
So miserable.
Miki,
would you rather have had Yota
just keep treating you as a friend?
Huh? What?! Why'd you-
It's Yota, isn't it?
I can tell just by looking.
Oh… So that means…
I was the only one who didn't notice it.
Throwing things around like
"friend," and… "I love you"…
I'm such a-
An insensitive jerk.
Why am I so awful?
What should I do?
I'm miserable.
Look, you can't blame yourself, Miki.
It's not his fault either.
I'd think that if you found out that
someone you thought of as just a friend
actually liked you in a
different way than you did…
And once you realized they
look at you in that way…
It would feel a bit disgusting,
wouldn't it?
CRACK
I find people tend to fall
without even realizing it's happening.
Once they're in love, even if the
other person doesn't feel the same…
And also…
Madam Koyun said
the people she considers friends would
never become potential love interests.
They're mentally prepared to
get hurt to some extent.
Seriously…
Who am I trying to convince here?
I…
These feelings I have…
I'm so hungry.
- Oh, hey there!
- Huh?
PEOPLE WHO STARTED MINGLING
AT SOME POINT IN THE CHEER SQUAD
This concert
is shaping up to be really fun!
Oh, You're coming too?
Yep!
I'm going with Amamiya.
OH, REALLY…?
Huh?
Are you two… a thing?
Oh, no, we're not.
We're planning to invite more
people so it's a group thing.
I'm pretty sure it's
his way of dodging me
cause I'm being pushy.
- Huh?
- See you later.
Is he dodging her or is it…
In her head?
Who knows, man?
Either way,
I'm worried she's gonna end up in tears.
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
Miki…
Do you have work today?
Hm? I don't.
Do you… Wanna hang out then?
Uh Sure.
She's the one… inviting me out?
There are so many things I
want to ask Miki about
But then… there's also
so much I haven't told her yet.
Especially about Amamiya.
But after hiding it for so long
it feels embarrassing to
suddenly bring it up now.
It's gonna come completely
out of left field.
With all these thoughts
jumbled up in my head…
I'm worried I'll trip over my
words and it'll come out all wrong.
Oh no, is this…
a serious conversation?
A consultation? What do I do?
The truth is… My feelings for Yota…
Is that what it is?!
What should I say, and how
much should I spill?
Yota?
You wanna… maybe grab some food?
Mm hm. Sounds good, I'm all yours buddy.
Oh… well… I didn't exactly
mean like for a venting session.
Ooh. These are the tastiest ones!
- Miki.
- Huh?
- Well, um…
- What did you get?
There's uh…
Something I wanna to talk to you about.
It's uh… About…
- Amamiy-
- Man, it's been forever.
C'mon Yota. Whenever I invite you out
you always turn me down.
Ah please, that's not true.
I think that might be-
No,
- it's definitely them.
- Really?
Fine, whatever, then.
- Yota!
- Amamiya!
So uh… Minato…
- Huh?
- Are you gonna go out with Kurita?
So, Minato
Hm?
Are you gonna go out with Kurita?
With Kurita?
- Who?
You mean Kuriki?
Huh? Uh,
Yeah, the first-year student.
Wait, why are you bringing her up?
You're going to the concert,
right? Just the two of you?
Eh, it's just a concert though.
Besides,
I was thinking of inviting more people.
So, you should come too.
Minato, hear me out.
Ever since junior high, you've always
gotten too flirty with girls,
which gets their hopes up
and leads them on.
Should we-
really be eavesdropping like this?
Well, it's too late to leave now.
You've had a zillion failed
relationships because of it.
Huh?
Here I was,
thinking that Yota had finally
come to confide in me about his problems.
But instead he's ripping me
a new one just like Miki did.
Wait so… you're saying…
I should start rejecting anyone I don't
necessarily have romantic feelings for?
If I don't hate that person,
don't you think I should at least
give them a chance?
I'm not saying you should go that far…
But,
just stop giving girls the wrong idea,
okay?
Is that cause-
you didn't like when it happened to you?
This has nothing to do with Miki!
I…
- Sorry.
- No, I'm sorry too…
I went too far.
Yota…
TEARS WELLING UP
Oh gosh…
I haven't even told Koyun anything yet…
Hang on, Minato. How much do you know?
Pretty much everything. Sorry.
I'm sorry for putting you
in such a weird position.
That's okay, no worries.
So, Minato…
- Huh?
- Have you ever fallen in love?
Fallen in love?
Yeah, like,
"no one can replace this person," or
"They're the only one for me,"
or something.
Honestly,
I feel that way about everyone!
Even about you and Miki.
You're both irreplaceable friends to me.
What about Koyun?
Koyun… Is great, isn't she?
The four of us have a great time together
and you two get along really well,
don't you? Do you think there might be…
something there?
Yeah. Koyun is very…
I like her.
As a friend, you know.
I really like her a lot.
Oh.
Well man, I hope one day
you feel that way about someone.
Hey, who knows.
I hope I can show you that side someday.
- Oh…
- I hate rainy season. It's so humid.
Koyun…
Miki, sorry…
But I-
Fell in love with him.
You- Yota-
I fell for Amamiya.
Wait, what?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Sorry I couldn't tell you.
I wasn't sure of my feelings yet.
And I didn't know what I even wanted so
I never told you.
Okay, wait… I can't…
Really? So…
This whole time, I was…
Don't try to put the
moves on her or be weird!
Yeah. This is a great idea!
Crap… This sucks… This is…
the crappiest crap that ever crapped.
I'm gonna barf.
Argh-
Um… Miki…
I promise you
I knew nothing was gonna come from it.
Plus, he just clearly said that
we're only friends, so don't worry.
Huh? No, wait.
I was referring to-
How I feel about myself.
Huh?
The whole time, I thought-
This was what was going.
And I thought-
Huh? B-B-But- back then, and I- and that-
- and this… And then you- but he was-
- Huh? But you seemed so- Oh,
I misread everything-
ALL MISUNDERSTANDINGS WERE CLEARED UP
So, does that mean this whole time
I've been screwing up Yota's love life?
No! That's not it!
Ultimately,
I always thought of Yota
and I as just friends.
Miki… previously,
you talked about maybe
being open to romance
and getting a boyfriend.
But you…
don't want that to be him?
Let's just say,
hypothetically,
if I confessed to you out of the blue
that I always liked you romantically,
do you think
you could just switch gears and say,
"Sure, I've never though of
you that way, but why not?"
Good point.
I just… knew I couldn't do that so easily.
Someone
confessing their love to me makes me
feel worse than I thought it would.
But… there's also a selfish part of me
that thinks it would be easier if
I could just learn to love someone
who loves me already.
I turned him down because I
thought I would hurt him
if my heart wasn't really in it.
But then I ended up hurting him anyway.
So then what should I have said to him?
Miki. Listen,
The way Yota feels towards you,
Isn't sexual.
SEXUAL DESIRE
His interactions with you were never
fueled by desire to date you or touch
- you, or hold you or anything physical.
- What are you saying?
He likes you for you.
He likes you as a friend too.
He genuinely sees you
and likes you for who you are.
This whole time,
the only thing on Yota's mind
has been how to make you happy.
He isn't thinking about
having "you" make "him" happy.
That's not who he is.
So then,
don't blame yourself for
anything that happens with Yota.
To me, you're Miki.
You're not just some girl.
Today… I…
When Yota came over
near where I was sitting
I- I looked away.
Starting tomorrow…
I'll be more-
Yeah.
CLICKETY CLACKETY
PUFFY EYES
What's your plan? So
Huh? Plan for what?
Minato.
Will you tell him how you feel?
No, no, no, n-no! Never! No way.
Oh-
Since I've known you,
This is the first time you've opened up
to me about something like this.
I wanna have your back and support you.
Well thank you.
Although
after finding out he only
sees me as a friend,
I think I want to shut my
feeling sdown while I still can.
I mean if you think about it
isn't it be better
to keep him as a friend?
Plus, I don't think someone like me
with no experience would be able to
win him over anyway.
HARD TO DENY
Let's all just hang out as friends again.
Yeah.
If I don't hate that person…
don't you think I should at
least give them a chance?
The kindness and affection
Minato gave so readily,
were the same he gave… to everyone.
I thought I was special and read into it.
I got carried away.
I'm just-
How… How could I be so stupid?
It's okay.
I'll…
I'll be alright.
Time to move on.
At the start, I didn't even
remotely want to date him anyway.
That's why
I was so distant when we first met.
And yet-
As a friend, you know.
I really like her a lot.
At the end of the day,
just hearing him say that
is more than enough for me.
And really,
maybe I should be questioning the nature
of my feelings in the first place.
I used to always be the one to
reject everyone around me so maybe
I was just feeling lonely.
If that's all it was then I'm okay.
If I'm happy how things are now
I won't feel lonely.
And it's not too late
to start back at square one.
Morning.
Uh-
Good morning.
GRADE 2 CLASS 2
Huh?
You're early today.
Good morning, Minato!
Woah, alright.
Morning to you too!
Oh. Good- good morning.
Hm?
Good morning, Yota!
I like the energy.
Morning.
If things stay this way
then my feelings…
are nothing more than a bad joke.
I mean, the thought of her maybe
seeing me the same way one day…
Is that even possible?